# Kakha Gujejiani

+995 598 82 92 72 | kakha.gujejiani.1@iliauni.edu.ge | linkedin.com/in/kakha | github.com/kakha

### **SUMMARY**

My first touch with the field of programming occurred during the quarantine period, which changed everything, since the quarantine period I have worked tirelessly on myself to develop and succeed in this interesting area. Learning each new technology is like a journey full of adventures, I have never experienced such pleasure in process of learning.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Junior Front-end Developer @Singular

May 2021 - Present

Duties and Responsibilities:

- Design and develop scalable frontend solutions for both web- and mobile platforms;
- Develop and debug modules and websites's specific features taking into account the technical constraints;
- Prioritize the user experience and develop features accordingly;
- Production and maintenance of websites and web application user interfaces;
- Creating tools that enhance interaction with the site in any browser;
- Testing the site for usability and fixing any bugs;

## Intern Front-end Developer @Singular

December 2020 - May 2021 (5 months)

The purpose of the internship was to learn the necessary technologies and concepts as efficiently as possible, and then apply the gained experience in the real world. my experience with React and JavaScript helped me quickly master the concepts of Angular and TypeScript.

#### **APPLICATIONS**

- \* Weight App The app is designed to help users control daily weight, meals, and activities in one place. App created using Angular and TypeScript
- \* Covid API using covid API and showing all country list with some information, the user can add the country to favorites, also when the user clicks country, it shows additional information about the currently clicked country
- \* TO-DO App To-Do list application, the user can choose UI, can add tasks by categories, and importance also can sort the daily tasks by importance, using local storage to save data.
- \* Github Search single page application for getting data and searching Github users, with Github public API, created in React and managing state with Redux
- \* Health-App managing state with Redux, using React-Router for navigation, sending http request with axios, and doing authentication using firebase API, saving user Information in Local-storage and reusing it in components.
- \* Bank-App single page application, created using by only functional Components, with React Hooks.

## @FreeCodeCamp Projects

created with React.js

Javascript Calculator | Promodo Clock | Quote Machine | Morkdown Previewer | Drum Machine

## @CodeHs final Project

Final Project - Arcade Game

**TECHNICAL SKILLS** 

Languages: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

Frameworks: Angular

Developer Tools: Git, SCSS, BEM, Visual Studio, Figma, XD

Libraries: React, Axios, Redux, NGRX, RxJS

**EDUCATION** 

### **Ilia State University**

2016 - 2021

MAY 2020 - Present

SCHOOL OF BUSINESS, TECHNOLOGY AND EDUCATION

BitCamp

SCHOOL OF SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, AND ENGINEERING

**Books** 

Just Javascript - Dan Abramov you don't know js - Kyle Simpson

#### HOBBIES

Football Swimming Chess Tennis Travel Running Movie/Anime